Cross account replication, s3 batch replication

Versioning should be enabled on both buckets
Replication config. (as XML) won't replicate objects that existed before adding config.
Replication config. should have destination bucket, and objects to be replicated
With objects it also replicates ACLs, the owner in destination remains same unless othersie stated
Objects that are already replicas, created by another CRR in the source, are not replicated.
AWS S3 replicates metadata from the source objects to the replicas only.
Delete marker replication should be disabled to protect against accidental or malicious deletes.

1. Create a role for source bucket and pass it in a replication rule for that source bucket
2. Attach bucket policy to destination bucket

...
    <Rule>
        <ID>Rule-1</ID>
        <Status>Enabled-or-Disabled</Status>
        <Filter>
            <Prefix></Prefix>   ///to select objects based on key-prefix and object tags 
        </Filter>
        <Priority>integer</Priority>
        <DeleteMarkerReplication>
           <Status>Enabled-or-Disabled</Status>
        </DeleteMarkerReplication>
        <Destination>
           <Bucket>arn:aws:s3:::DOC-EXAMPLE-BUCKET</Bucket> 
        </Destination>    
    </Rule>
    <Rule>
         ...
    </Rule>
     ...
...

...
<Destination>
       <Bucket>arn:aws:s3:::DOC-EXAMPLE-BUCKET</Bucket>
       <StorageClass>storage-class</StorageClass>
</Destination>
...

Replicating existing objects
   done through the use of a Batch Operations job.
   Source bucket must have existing replication configuration.
   IAM role for batch Operations job
   AWS S3 manifest
Batch Operations ( from S3 Batch Operations home page )
    A manifest or an inventory report is needed that contains objects to replicate
    Re-replication of deleted objects with version id in destination is not supported (use Batch Operations Copy)
Manifest
    specify keys to act upon and version id
    same Prefix and tags as replication configuration 
Filters for a Batch Replication job
    You can filter objects to replicate based on the "ObjectReplicationStatuses" value
    If you want to both replicate existing objects and retry replicating objects that previously failed to replicate, include both "NONE" and "FAILED".
    we can create Batch Operations job at the time of 1st rule creation.
    After job is created, it enters in "Awaiting your confirmation to run" state
Question
    What if some objects have different versions, will all of the versions be replicated when our config is already there.
